(Howard:)The book says at this stage
of the pregnancy
(Howard:)morning sickness
should be going away.
(Howard:)So that's good news, right?
(Bernadette(pff):)The only thing I hate more than
you right now is that book!
There she is!
(Howard:)Who's ready for a hot,
(Howard:)three-hour car ride
to the desert?
(Bernadette:)Next vomit is gonna be
in your lap.
(Amy:)I'm sorry.
(Howard:)We don't have to go.
(Bernadette:)But it's our last chance
to take a vacation
(Bernadette:)that's just the two of us.
(Howard:)How 'bout we stay here?
(Howard:)We don't even have
to tell anyone.
(Howard:)It'll be like
a secret vacation at home.
(Bernadette:)Keeping secrets
from our friends--
that does sound
kinda fun.
(Howard:)Does it sound... sexy?